October 11th, Stellar Year 2149
- Time Since Mission Began -
Let's go.
Frederica.
If I told you to ignore everybody
but that idiot and go, could you?
Yes.
They just don't give up.
What about the Löwes?
Still following us.
They're traveling along the river
below the cliffs.
How much longer until the Morpho?
15K as the crow flies.
It moved a little and stopped.
I don't know why, but we'll use
this opportunity to get close.
It seems to be after something.
Below! They're firing!
Anju!
I'm fine.
I'm not damaged.
But... sorry. I don't think
I can climb back up.
Wait! I'll use my wire to...
There's no time.
I'll handle them.
You guys go.
Fido.
Leave all the spare missile pods you've got.
More are coming.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Stay safe.
Now then...
Time to get to work.
How we looking?
We shook them off, but another group
is trying to block our path.
They really don't give up.
They'll get in our way when
we're fighting the Morpho, won't they?
Once we're past this,
it's just open plains, right?
I'm only useful in places like this.
So I'll be a decoy here.
I'll be as careful as I can. Hang in there.
They've split their group even more?
I'm bringing shame
to the Nouzen clan,
letting mere common soldiers
like them find me.
However...
I'll give you credit for being cold enough
to abandon your friends as you get closer.
Pale Rider to wide-area network!
Now executing the designated
bombardment schedule.
No further communications will be allowed
until the schedule is complete.
I'm about to meet a comrade.
No one will interfere!
No one!
Dodge!
He can shoot multiple rounds like that?
Crap!
Go on, quick!
That was scattershot.
It won't deal heavy damage!
A counterattack is incoming!
What about you?
I can provide more support from here,
because it's easier to see.
Get close while his attacks
aren't concentrated!
Go!
Understood.
Thanks.
Leave it to me.
I'm tired of these little flies.
Even those who aren't invited
are getting close.
Anyone who interferes
must be eliminated immediately!
Kurena!
Raiden, above us.
Raiden!
What's wrong?
He was trying to protect me!
Don't worry.
It won't kill me.
But... sorry.
I'm out of the game now, too.
Frederica, get aboard Fido.
Wehrwolf lost the legs
on its right side.
It can't go any farther.
Raiden...
Go.
The next attack is coming.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it.
Don't die.
Sure.
Fido.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
You're staying here.
Fido will stay and hide.
Shinei!
If something happens to me,
take Frederica back to base.
Don't worry about recovering the others.
Get her back to the Federacy.
Open up, Fido!
I need to tell that idiot directly.
Frederica.
You're scared to lose him, but you want to save him anyway, right?
Your knight.
Survive, so you can do that.
I knew you'd come.
I can't wait to rip you apart!
Now, come to me!
Come! Come!
So...
Don't try to fight on your own.
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Incredible moves...
Just as I was hoping for!
I'm still too far away?
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
When I'm fighting,
I can forget everything.
Yeah. It's nice and peaceful.
I'm sorry.
You want to go help your master, right?
If it weren't for me...
Let's at least watch
their battle to the end.
You think I can't shoot you now?
He was trying to make me overheat
from the beginning?
A plan worthy of the eldest sons
of the Nouzen.
If you'd been by my side,
the Empire would yet stand.
I'd love to have your power
on our side.
But I guess you're too strong
to take that risk.
Yes, you have to get close
to pierce my armor with those tiny guns.
But don't you think
you're being a little reckless?
Do you know about Shin's
legendary point-blank shot?
He sent a Vánagandr flying
during a mock battle at school.
He did it to avoid a collision,
but he failed due to dangerous piloting.
Oh, yeah? Tell me more.
That's right.
I wasn't surprised then.
Because I knew already...
There's another person out there
who can do the impossible in a Feldreß.
No, Shinei!
Don't get close to him!
Kiri was just like you!
Close combat was his specialty!
Shin!
Get back!
Don't interfere!
Raiden!
Enough, Raiden!
Run!
One round left.
Engines at their limit.
Wingmen all down.
I'm all that's left.
The enemy is unharmed.
Enemy main guns and subweapons
are still functional.
This may be... the end, yeah.
Go, everyone.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm on it.
Don't die.
I won't forget!
While you still can, huh?
You're still interfering?
Don't you dare!
You won't let me get close,
no matter what, huh?
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
I can fight!
Pierce me with a hail of bullets,
rip my body apart, and I can still fight!
Maybe I'll die here, but...
But I can still kill them all!
Why?
Why do you insist on fighting?
Why are you trying to kill everyone?
You don't know his name.
You don't know his face.
But he shares your blood.
He's the only comrade you have!
You know why...
Because this is all I have left!
All I have is the battle.
The battlefield that burns in my veins.
It burns my soul to ash,
so only the empty,
smoldering flames of war remain.
Yes...
On that day, I lost everything!
Even you!
If you...
If you're going to be the same...
If you're going to be like me,
then it's better that...
Fool!
Have you forgotten your master's face,
Kiriya Nouzen?
Princess...
Stop fighting, Kiri!
You have no reason to fight!
Princess, what are you saying?
Enough...
You've done enough.
You've done well, my knight.
You!
Not only did you destroy my Empire
and steal its crown,
but now you're using the young princess
as a hostage?
Kiri! Stop it, Kiri!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Kiri...
Look at me, Kiri!
What's wrong, my knight?
Come on. Save me.
Princess! What are you doing, Princess?
Princess! Princess!
We finally meet again, and you...
Kiri!
Princess!
Now!
Frederica.
Where is your knight?
Kiri is...
Behind the main gun.
Between the first pair of wings!
Farewell.
"Shin."